&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们深入练习这个模块模式
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's dive into an exercise to practice this module pattern
我们刚刚得知的。
that we've just learned about.
在本练习中，您将重构一些管理
In this exercise, you are gonna be refactoring some code that manages
车间的注册记录。
the enrollment records for a workshop.
你不会改变功能，但是
You're not gonna be changing the functionality, but
您将重新排列代码，以使用我们所学到的经典或
you are gonna be rearranging the code, to use what we learned about the classic or
显示模块模式。
the revealing module pattern.
顺便说一下，作为奖励，
As a bonus, by the way,
也可以尝试使用ES6模块语法重写它，
feel free to also try re-writing this using the ES6 module syntax,
在您完成练习的原始版本之后。
after you've done the original version of the exercise.
所以，你的说明放在这里，它应该是相当直接的，但是
So, your instructions are laid out here, it should be fairly straightforward but
您的说明包括定义模块工厂函数
your instructions include defining a module factory function
称为定义工作坊，它将制作和
called defineWorkshop, that's going to make and
返回那些代表公共API的对象实例。
return those object instances that represent the public API's.
这五个方法或函数是需要在公共API上公开的，
These five methods or functions are what needs to be exposed on the public API,
你最终会定义这些函数。
and you're going to end up defining those functions.
所以这些是不存在的。
So these are ones that don't exist.
您将在公共API中公开它们，然后定义它们。
You're gonna expose them in the public API and then define them.
然后您将移动currentEnrollment和StudentRecords
And you're going to move the currentEnrollment and studentRecords
数组添加到模块中，但它们需要是模块内部的空数组。
arrays into the module, but they need to be empty arrays inside of the module.
然后从外部使用addStudent和
And then you're going to from the outside use the addStudent and
entrlStudent函数将数据推送到模块实例中，好吗？
enrollStudent functions to push the data into your module instance, okay?
所以我们不会把数据嵌入到一个毫无意义的模块中，
So we're not gonna embed data into a module that doesn't make any sense,
或者将数据硬编码到模块中。
or hard code data into a module.
因此，您将在这里将所有这些对数组的赋值更改为函数调用。
So you'll change all of those assignments to the array into function calls here.
然后我们将使用定义的工作坊来制作一个模块
And then we're going to use that defineWorkshop to make a module
实例名为Deep JS。
instance called deepJS.
然后我们将多次调用Deep JS.addStudent来添加学生记录，
Then we'll call deepJS.addstudent multiple times to add in the student records,
我们将多次调用Deep JS.entrlStudent来注册它们。
we'll call deepJS.enrollStudent several times to enroll them.
然后我们将更改对其他可执行文件的引用，
And then we will change the references to the other executables,
到它们在Deep JS模块API上的对应部分。
to their counterparts on the deepJS module API.
这就是对你正在做的事情的概述。
So that's an overview of what you're doing.
如果你看一下EXJS文件，这就是它看起来的样子，
if you look at the EXJS file, this is what it looks like,
功能在底部，通常它们被拆分并提升。
the functions are at the bottom, and generally they are split out and hoisted.
你只是简单地接受这个文件，而不是改变它本身的行为，
And you're simply taking this file not changing it's behavior per se,
但将其格式化为模块。
but formatting this as a module.
你试图在这里获得的好处是
The take away that you're trying to get here is the advantages of
模块模式隐藏了不需要公开的细节。
the module pattern, are hiding details that aren't necessary to be exposed.
没有必要
It is not necessary for
任何人都知道数组是跟踪当前注册的对象。
anybody to know that an array is what is tracking the current enrollments.
或者有一组跟踪当前学生记录的对象。
Or that there's an array of objects tracking the current student records.
这是一个实现细节，并且
That is an implementation detail, and
所有的软件工程都告诉我们应该隐藏起来。
all manner of software engineering tells that ought to be hidden.
这样它就可以在将来被重构，这样它就不会被滥用。
So that it can be future refactored, so that it can't be abused.
所以这里的想法是使用模型模式来隐藏必要的细节，
So the idea here is use the model pattern to hide the details that are necessary,
只公开那些必要的公共IP方法。
only expose those public IP methods that's necessary.